AGGELOS DIAMANTOPOULOS

PHP Developer



5 07.08.1995





+306987564060 @ diam5752@gmail.com

SOCIAL MEDIA







http://github.com/diam5752



PROFILE

Software Developer with more than 5 years of experience in programming (mainly PHP and C++). **Most Recent position**: CTO and co-owner of the startup Trappveling, leading a small team. The application is released in Play Store and Apple Store (currently in Beta but online in the stores for download).

EDUCATION

10.2013 - 06.2019

Master in Computer Engineering and Informatics Department, Patras, Greece

EXPERIENCE

08.2018 - 08.2019

Trappveling, Valencia, Spain

CTO and co-Owner of Trappveling

I was in charge for everything (design architecture, development, servers, database, testing) that has to do with the development of a mobile application named Trappveling, except for the front end part. Tech: PHP7+, Laravel, Docker, MySQL, Git, Linux, AWS S3 Storage, AWS RDS Database, Composer, Postman, PHPUnit Testing, Kraken.io, google Maps API, google Places API, weather API ...

04.2018 - 07.2018

Citrix, Patras, Greece

Software Developer

Worked on one of the main company's tools, Citrix Netscaler. I worked in C++ programming language , mainly in Linux environment, maintaining connection between servers and handling the data transportation between them. My main task was to implement an API, the logstreamdumper, which purpose was to transfer the log data from Citrix Netscaler to NSULFD process running on NetScaler MAS and NetScaler Insight Center, efficiently and in a useful way, by eliminating the need for knowledge of information (like headers type) between transactions before they happen, thus making the tool more dynamic.

01.2017 - 05.2017

University Of Patras

C++ Tutor

Teaching object oriented programming (focused on C++ language) in University students under the supervision of professor Tsakalidis Athanasios.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

PHP
C++

MySQL

HTML5,CSS,bootstrap

Ajax,JQuery,Javascript

REST,API's

AWS (S3,ElasticBeans,EC2 ...)

Git (version controlling)

Composer

Laravel

Docker

Algorithms & Data Structures

PROJECTS

Unix

Unit Testing

- ✓ Trappveling APP (iOS and Android)
 - An application with the use of modern technologies such as docker, AWS S3, ElasticBeanstalk and many more, currently on stores in Beta version.
 - Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.anvalu.trappveling iOS: https://itunes.apple.com/es/app/trappveling/id1456190244?mt=8
- ✓ Thesis: "Dynamic Planar Range Maxima Queries"

 Implemented in c++ and is about finding in optimal time the maximal points among a set of points and making operations in the created data structure. Also created testers for each internal data structure used.
- ✓ "Implementation of an online delivery platform"

 Using PHP, Ajax, javascript, JQuery and SQL, created a completely functional online delivery platoform (front end and back end) with features as:

 Maps (google API), QR scan and many more.
- ✓ e-ShopUniversity project made with OpenCart
- ✓ For more projects:
 https://github.com/diam5752

LANGUAGES

English (Proficiency Level) Greek (Native Speaker)



HOBBY







Technology

Drums

Chess